pkware.com 2018-08-12

# Privacy Policy | Smartcrypt | PKWARE

PKWARE, Inc. ("PKWARE") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Website Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes what information PKWARE collects from visitors to its websites and how PKWARE uses such information.

* * *

This Privacy Policy applies to the following website(s) owned and controlled by PKWARE: www.pkware.com, www.viivo.it, www.viivo.com, www.smartcrypt.com or any other domain controlled by PKWARE (collectively, the "Websites", or individually, a "Website"). By accessing a Website, you acknowledge and fully agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website owned or operated by any third party vendor, retailer, supplier, service provider or affiliate, even if such third party websites link to a Website owned by PKWARE, or a Website owned by PKWARE contains links to a third party website. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and PKWARE is not responsible for, the practices of any third party, affiliate or business partner that PKWARE does not own or control. Additionally, the owners of social media services may have additional online privacy terms and conditions that supersede this Privacy Policy depending on a user's own personal preferences with that social media provider.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any software applications or products sold, licensed or distributed by PKWARE, even if such software applications may be obtained from a Website. Certain PKWARE software applications may collect and report to PKWAREdata or information such as total activated licenses, anonymized Software usage statistics, email domains, user credentials, and/or public encryption key(s). The terms and conditions regarding any software application shall be set forth in the particular software license agreement for such software application.

* * *

If you browse a Website without creating a user account, purchasing any products or services or sending an e-mail to PKWARE using a form located on a Website, you do so anonymously. PKWARE does not collect your e-mail address or other personal information. PKWARE does log your IP address (the internet address of your computer) to determine which parts of the Websites you visit and how long you spend there. PKWARE does not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable; however, we do track approximate geographic information based on IP address, the date and time you visited and the type of computer, operating system and web browser you are using. Your browser supplies us with this information.

PKWARE uses this information from our server logs to learn more about our visitors as a group, not about you as an individual. The information helps us identify overall usage patterns and trends on the Websites, administer its Websites, improve content and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. PKWARE uses third party services, such as Google Analytics, to provide PKWARE with Website traffic analysis. Such third party services do not collect personally identifiable information. PKWARE will not sell personally identifiable information to third parties without your permission.

* * *

Throughout the Websites there are several forms that request information and/or allow you to purchase products and services or enter giveaways. When you complete these forms, PKWARE will request some personal information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or fax number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, PKWARE or its agent will request financial information. Any financial information collected is used only to bill you for the products you are purchasing. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of forms, PKWARE will ask for relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to allow for PKWARE to provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. PKWARE reserves the right to use the e-mail address provided by you to inform you of other available products or services, or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings from PKWARE by following the procedures detailed in the Choice/Opt-out section located below or in any of the e-mail message(s) you may receive from PKWARE.

By providing PKWARE with such information, you give PKWARE permission to contact you or use the information you provide for the specific purpose stated at the time you provide such information to PKWARE. PKWARE will not disclose personally identifiable information it collects from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

  * To fulfill your requests for services
  * To protect PKWARE from liability
  * To respond to legal processes or comply with law, or   
In connection with a merger, acquisition or liquidation of PKWARE

* * *

PKWARE may use cookies throughout its Websites to remember a visitor's preferences on their next visit, to improve search functionality or to hold information that you would otherwise need to re-key. PKWARE reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with its partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on its Website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into a Website that relies on third-party cookies). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on the PKWARE Website.

* * *

PKWARE does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals or mechanisms.

* * *

PKWARE web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow PKWARE to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. PKWARE may also include web beacons in promotional email messages or newsletters in order to determine whether such messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of PKWARE advertising campaigns or e-mail communications. These web beacons may be used by such service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or e-mails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables PKWARE and its service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to a Website and how you use the Website. PKWARE prohibits web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

* * *

The Website has commercially reasonable technical and organizational security measures in place with the intent prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information under PKWARE control. However, PKWARE cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat such security measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. PKWARE is under no obligation to monitor the conduct of its Website users, but it will investigate and respond when violations are reported. PKWARE reserves the right to delete, remove or exclude any listing or information, in its sole discretion, that does not meet its intent and guidelines for the services offered on the Website.

* * *

This Privacy Policy, and PKWARE's collection and use of customer information, shall be governed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the United States and the State of Wisconsin. Any disputes arising out of this Policy shall be adjudicated in Milwaukee County, Wisconsin or federal court of competent jurisdiction in the Eastern District of the State of Wisconsin.

* * *

Any translation of this Privacy Policy is done for local requirements and in the event of a dispute between the English and any non-English versions, the English version of this Privacy Policy shall govern.

* * *

You may opt-out of receiving further communications from PKWARE through any of the following methods:

  * Use the opt-out link found at the bottom of an email message you receive from PKWARE; or
  * Send a request by email to: [marketing@pkware.com](mailto:marketing@pkware.com) ; or   
Call +1.414.289.9788

* * *
